creativecircle.com 2015-09-06

# Creative Circle > Privacy Policy

#### Our Commitment to Privacy 

Creative Circle, LLC ("we," "us" or "our") respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us as described under “Questions” below. If our Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will post an updated Privacy Policy on our website. You can tell if the Privacy Policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears at the end of this Privacy Policy. 

##### Information We Collect 

When you create an account with us and/or apply for a job, we ask for personal information such as: 

  * Your name, email address, residence and mailing address, phone number and other contact information;
  * Information about your current employment and former employment, including experience, title, compensation, etc.;
  * Your education, training, skills and abilities; and
  * The type of job or assignment you are seeking and when you can start work.

You also may elect to upload a resume or curriculum vitae or apply for a position on our site, in which case we will have the information you provide to us in that process. We may combine information we collect about you with other information we receive from additional sources, such as information you may have provided to us by other means or information collected by our job placement consultants. 

##### How We Use Your Information 

We use your information to provide you with job placement services. We also may use your information for a variety of related purposes and other business functions, such as, but not limited to the following: 

  * To provide you with information and communicate with you, including about available positions;
  * To provide you with our job placement, training, career counseling, or career transition services;
  * To arrange employment or temporary assignments for you;
  * To inform our clients, candidates and business partners about our services;
  * To help us administer or improve our business and our services;
  * To perform certain research and analyses;
  * To collect aggregate statistical information regarding the use of our site;
  * To protect the integrity of or to improve our websites, information systems, and security; and
  * For certain administrative purposes, such as risk management, to fulfill or address legal and compliance obligations, and to resolve or defend legal claims.

##### Information We Share

We may share the personal information we collect about you with other parties. For example, we may share information about you with our clients in order to identify appropriate job opportunities for you. We also may share your information:

  * With our subsidiaries and affiliates;
  * With clients who may have job opportunities available or interest in hiring or placing our candidates;
  * With our service providers, such as third party vendors and hosting partners who provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run our site;
  * When reasonably requested or required by law enforcement authorities or other government officials;
  * When otherwise required by law or in response to legal process;
  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss;
  * When reasonably necessary to an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity;
  * As needed to protect the vital interests of an individual; and
  * In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets.

If you are a resident of California, you may ask us to refrain from sharing your information with third parties and among our affiliates for marketing purposes. Let us know your preference by contacting us as described under “Questions” below. 

##### Cookies 

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies as part of our service. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies.

##### Information Security 

We maintain administrative, physical, and technical safeguards intended to protect against the loss, misuse, or unauthorized access, acquisition, alteration or destruction of information we collect through physical and automated means. Your account is protected by your log-in information, which you must keep secure and confidential. 

##### Links to Other Sites

We may provide links to websites which may not be owned, controlled, or operated by us. Your use of these other sites will be governed by the privacy policies and terms of use of such sites which you should carefully review before using such sites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites, your use of them, or the information practices of their operators. 

##### Questions 

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [termsofuse@creativecircle.com](mailto:termsofuse@creativecircle.com) or by mail at: 

5750 Wilshire Boulevard, Suite 610, Los Angeles, CA 90036. 

(Revised April 27, 2012)
